Bowers, Kate. Everything but the kitchen sink: an inventory (titleproper in titlestatement in filedesc) ||| Resource (call) |||.Ident (num) |||
Finding aid filing title |||
Harvard University Archives
Title (i.e. Everything but the kitchen sink, unitttitle) |||
Bulk, 1989-1999
Date expression (AT outputs this instead of date range as EAD, uses date range if this empty)|||
Resource (call) |||.Ident (num) |||
Harvard University Archives
1.0 Cubic feet Container summary|||
Abstract without a label content -- 1st note input, 2nd note on "Notes etc" tab: |||
3rd note input: abstract content|||
Dimensions note no label |||
Dimensions note with label text of content|||
General physical description note no label |||
Material specific details note no label |||
Physical facet note no label |||
Bowers, Kate, 1963- |||
Test|||, Name|||, Ms.|||, Number|||, Suffix|||, Title|||, (Fuller form|||), 1880-1980|||, qualifier|||
Box Container 1 indicator (is this container tag?) |||
Separated Materials label |||
Separated Materials note content 1st note in "Notes, etc" tab, umpteenth note added, but dragged to first note position in notes tab in AT. It appears that the note order in AT has some impact on the note order in the resulting EAD. It looks as if those notes that go outside the DID are exporting simply in the order in which they appear in AT. |||
Kate's -- note -- about -- input |||
All generic text I added is meant to indicate the type of input field in the AT. Text I added has three pipes at the end of it ||| unless it was impossible due to the type of data (numeric). Data from related tables (e.g. Repository name) does not have three pipes, nor does text generated from the style sheet. I did not use pipes in text from real-world examples.
Accruals note
Accruals content without label -- 2nd note input, 3rd note on "Notes, etc." tab: |||
Accruals note label|||
Accruals note content. 4th note input. |||
Appraisal note
Appraisal note without a label content |||
Appraisal note label|||
Apprasal note content. 6th note input. |||
Arrangement note label |||
Arrangement note content |||
Bibliography
Bibliography note no "title" content ||| 5th note input. Can be wrapped in tags thus (but why not bibref?): content in blockquote||| content in corpname||| content in date||| content in emph with bold italic selected ||| content in extref ||| content in famname||| content in function|||
Bibliography note "Title" area (in other notes this box is labeled "label") |||
Note in bibliography. wrapped text in persname (i.e. author||| wrapped text in title render italic wrapped text in geogname wrapped text in corpname (i.e. publisher) wrapped text in date (i.e. pub date) 9th note input. |||
Arrangement note
Arrangement note content. 7th note input, then dragged and dropped. No label. |||
Biographical/Historical note
Biographical historical note without label content. Note inserted placement by clicking in list of notes. |||
Biographical historical note label |||
Biographical historical note content |||
BiogHist with Chronlist label |||
Chronlogy Title |||
1991 ||| 1991 event 1 ||| 1991 event 2 ||| 1991 wrapped in title tag event 3 |||
1992 1992 event |||
1993 1993 event |||
Conditions Governing Access note
Conditions governing access note content no label |||
Conditions governing access note label (accessrestrict) |||
Conditions governing access note content (accessrestrict). 8th note input. |||
Custodial History note
Custodial history note content no label |||
Custodial history label |||
Custodial history content |||
Existence and Location of Copies note
Existnce and location of copies note no label |||
Existence and Location of Originals note
Existence and location of originals note no label |||
File Plan note
File plan note no label |||
File Plan Note label |||
File Plan note content |||
General note
General note content no label |||
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
Acquisition information note content no label content wrapped in corpname tag |||
Acquisition information note label |||
Acquisition information note content |||
Index title|||
Index note |||
Item value in index 1 ||| Reference text 1 |||
Item value in index 2 ||| Reference text 2 |||
Item value in index Series 3 folder 1 ||| Reference Text in index to series 3 folder 1 |||
Legal Status note
Legal status note no label |||
General note label |||
General note content |||
Other Finding Aids note
Other finding aids note content no label |||
Other finding aids note label |||
Other finding aids note content (otherfindaid) |||
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Physical Characteristics and Technical requirements note content |||
Related archival materials note label |||
Related archival materials note content |||
Related Archival Materials note
Related archival materials note content no label |||
Scope and Contents note
Scope and contents note content no label |||
Scope and contents label |||
Scope and contents note content |||
Separated Materials note
Separated materials note content no label |||
Acme Publishing (Boston, Mass.).; Engelhart, Anne; Test|||, Name|||, Ms.|||, Number|||, Suffix|||, Title|||, (Fuller form|||), 1880-1980|||, qualifier|||; Zinsser, Thomas; Aged women--United States
- Series title of series with Series-level notes with labels |||, 1880-1900; Series I |||; 2.0 Cubic feet; Series-level abstract text|||; Series-level dimensions text |||; Series-level general physical description text |||; Series-level material specific details text|||; Series-level physical facet text|||; Ginsburg, Ruth Bader|||
  Series-level accruals label|||
  Series-level accruals text|||
  Series-level appraisal label|||
  Series-level appraisal text|||
  Series-level arrangement label|||
  Series-level arrangement text|||
  Series-level bibliogrpahy title
  Series-level bibliogrphy note|||
  Series-level biographical/historical label|||
  Series-level biographical/historical text|||
  Series-level conditions governing access label|||
  Series-level conditions governing access text|||
  Series-level custodial history label |||
  Series-level custodial history text |||
  Series-level existence of copies label |||
  Series-level existence of copies text |||
  Series-level existence of originals label |||
  Series-level existence of originals text ||
  Series-level file plan label |||
  Series-level file plan text |||
  Series-level general note label |||
  Series-level general note text |||
  Series-level immediate source of acquisition label |||
  Series-level immediate source of acquisition text |||
  Series-level legal status label|||
  Series-level legal status text|||
  Series-level other finding aid label|||
  Series-level other finding aid text|||
  Series-level physical characteristics and technical requirements label|||
  Series-level physical characteristics and technical requirements text|||
  Series-level related materials label|||
  Series-level related materials text|||
  Series-level scope content label|||
  Series-level scope content text|||
  Series-level separated materials label|||
  Series-level separated materials text|||
- Series title of Series with Series-level notes without labels|||, Series II |||; 3.0 Linear feet; abstract, series-level text, no label |||; dimensions, series-level text, no label |||; general physical description, series-level text, no label |||; material specific details, series-level text, no label |||; physical facet, series-level text, no label |||
  Accruals note
  accruals, series-level text, no label |||
  Appraisal note
  appraisal, series-level text, no label |||
  Arrangement note
  arrangement, series-level text, no label |||
  Bibliography
  bibliography, series-level text, no label |||
  Biographical/Historical note
  biographical historical note, series-level text, no label |||
  Conditions Governing Access note
  conditions governing access, series-level text, no label |||
  Custodial History note
  custodial history, series-level text, no label |||
  Existence and Location of Copies note
  existence of copies, series-level text, no label |||
  Existence and Location of Originals note
  existence of originals, series-level text, no label |||
  File Plan note
  file plan, series-level text, no label |||
  General note
  general note, series-level text, no label |||
  Immediate Source of Acquisition note
  immediate source of acquisition, series-level text, no label |||
  Legal Status note
  legal status, series-level text, no label |||
  Other Finding Aids note
  other finding aid, series-level text, no label |||
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
  physical characteristics and technical requirements, series-level text, no label |||
  Related Archival Materials note
  related materials, series-level text, no label |||
  Scope and Contents note
  scope content, series-level text, no label |||
  Separated Materials note
  separated materials, series-level text, no label |||
  - Item title of item with Item-level notes, labled and unlabeled |||, ca. 1880-1900; Item 1 |||; Abstract note content at folder level, no label |||; Abstract note content at folder level|||; Dimensions note content at folder level, no label |||; Dimensions note content at folder level |||; General physical description note content at folder level, no label |||; General physical description note content at folder level |||
    Accruals note content at folder level, no label |||
    Accruals note label at folder level |||
    Accruals note content at folder level |||
    Appraisal note content at folder level, no label |||
    Appraisal note label at folder level |||
    Appraisal note content at folder level |||
    Arrangement note content at folder level |||
    Arrangement note label at folder level |||
    Bibliography note at folder level, no title |||
    Bibliography title at folder level
    Bibliography note content at folder level |||
    Bibliography item at folder level
    Biographical/historical note content at folder level, no label |||
    Biographical/historical note label at folder level |||
    Biographical/historical note content at folder level |||
    Conditions governing accessl note content at folder level, no label |||
    Conditions governing access label at folder level |||
    Conditions governing access note content at folder level |||
    Custodial history note content at folder level, no label |||
    Custodial history note label at folder level |||
    Custodial history note content at folder level |||
    Copies note content at folder level, no label |||
    Copies note label at folder level |||
    Copies note content at folder level |||
    ORiginals note content at folder level, no label |||
    Originals note label at folder level |||
    ORiginals note content at folder level |||
    File plan note content at folder level, no label |||
    File plan note label at folder level |||
    General note content at folder level, no label |||
    General note label at folder level
    General note content at folder level |||
    Multi-part general note label |||
    Ordered List title
    Ordered list item 1
    Ordered list item 2
    Ordered list item 3
    Ordered list item 4
    Ordered list item 5
- Series title of Series with Generic instances, box-folder type numbering|||, Series III |||
  - Folder title of Folder 1|||, Folder I |||
  - Folder title of Folder 2|||, 1880-1900; Folder 2 ||| (Box-folder 1.2)
  - Folder title of Folder 3 |||, ca. 1880; Folder 3 ||| (Box-folder 1.3)
  - Folder title of Folder 4|||, Folder 4 ||| (Box-folder 1.4)
  - Folder title of Folder 5 |||, Folder 5 ||| (Box-folder 1.5)
  - Folder title of Folder 6 |||, Folder 6 ||| (Box-folder 1.6)
- Series title of series with Generic instances, boxes and folders in separate fields in instances This text is wrapped in title tag |||, ca. 1880-1900|||; Series IV |||; 1.0 Cubic feet
  - Folder title of Folder 1 |||, ca. 1880-1900; UniqueID1|||; 0.1 Linear feet (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Folder title of Folder 2 |||, 1880-1900; UniqueID2||| (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Folder title of Folder 3 |||, ca. 1880; UniqueID3||| (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Folder title of Folder 4 |||, 1880; UniqueID4||| (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Folder title of Folder 5 |||, 1880; UniqueID5||| (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Folder title of Folder 6 |||, 1880; UniqueID6||| (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Folder title of Folder 7 (folder with a container summary) |||, 1890; UniqueID7|||; 2 folders (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Folder title of Folder 8 (folder with a footage) |||, 1890; UniqueID8|||; 2.0 Linear feet (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Series title of series with Generic folders, no instances, unique identifiers instead |||, 1880-1890; Series V |||
  - Folder title of Folder 1 |||, UniqueID3.1|||
  - Folder title of Folder 2 |||, UniqueID3.2|||
  - Folder title of Folder 3 |||, UniqueID3.3|||
  - Folder title of Folder 4 |||, UniqueID3.4|||
  - Folder title of Folder 5 |||, UniqueID3.5|||
  - Folder title of Folder 6 |||, UniqueID3.6|||
  - Folder title of Folder 7 |||, UniqueID3.7|||
  - Folder title of Folder 8 |||, UniqueID3.8|||
  - Folder title of Folder 9 |||, UniqueID3.9|||
  - Folder title of Folder 10 |||, UniqueID3.10|||
  - Folder title of Folder 11 |||, UniqueID3.11|||
  - Folder title of Folder 12 |||, UniqueID3.12|||
  - Folder title of Folder 13 |||, UniqueID3.13|||
  - Folder title of Folder 14 |||, UniqueID3.14|||
  - Folder title of Folder 15 |||, UniqueID3.15|||
- ELIZABETH BLODGETT AND LIVINGSTON HALL, 1823-2006; Series VI |||
  Storage Units Summary
  File units:
  1.1 through 28.2
  Memorabilia:
  85.1m
  Oversized folders
  Box 87, Folders 1-4
  Box F+87, Folders 1-4
  Folio drawer
  1
  Audio tapes
  T-354 reels 1 and 2